revelresorts.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Revel | Atlantic City, New Jersey Hotel & Casino

This Privacy Policy describes the information collection procedures and use of such information by Revel Entertainment Group LLC ("Revel"). Certain information is collected automatically, when you visit our website to read or browse through website material or to download information:

Revel will collect and store the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the browser software and operating system of your computer, the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to Revel's site. We will also record the date and time you accessed Revel's site.

"Cookies" are text files placed in your computer's browser to store certain preferences and information, which may enhance your browsing experience on Revel websites. Cookies may be used to personalize your website experience, such as recognizing you by name when you return. Revel does not use Cookies to track or collect personal identification information from website users. If you desire, instructions for your browser will allow you to make certain settings on your computer to warn you before a Cookie is stored, block all Cookies or erase Cookies from your hard drive. Other information is collected when you volunteer to identify yourself, and provide requested information:

You may choose to write to us, or fill out certain forms or online data requests, which provide your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information regarding a reservation at Revel, and related information. Revel uses this information to respond to your questions and requests. If you share with us, or consent to our collection of any personally identifying information about you, Revel may store it and use it for marketing, research and other business purposes, and we may associate your personal information with other information that we collect about you, such as details about your usage patterns and interests.

Similar information may be used to accept your entry into a particular consumer promotion. Revel may also use such data for market and consumer studies regarding product types, demographics and consumer preferences.

Revel may share your personal information with our service providers and marketing partners for use in connection with our programs, services and offerings. However, we will not sell your information to any other business without your consent except in order for you to continue to receive the benefits of any program, club or service. If your provide personal information to Revel for the purpose of receiving information about our special events or programs at our resort, we may provide your personal information to a third party that buys, that buys rents, or assumes responsibility for those events or programs at our resort.

All of the consumer and customer data collected by Revel is stored on a secured server to protect against unauthorized use and access. If you contact us regarding identity theft or some other form of unauthorized use, Revel may disclose pertinent information to law enforcement agencies and other third parties with responsibility and authority to investigate such a claim. Revel may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we do, we will post a notice of the changes on our website. You are responsible for checking the site for notices and updates. If you do not approve of any changes that Revel makes to our privacy policy, you may notify us to remove your personal information from our website.

Special note to Parents: all Revel websites are restricted to persons 21 years and older. Revel has no intention to collect any personal information, voluntary or involuntary, from children or any person below the age of 21. Parents are advised to warn their children against access to this site. All users of Revel websites consent to this Policy. You may update or change information about yourself, or forward any other questions or concerns about this Policy by contacting Revel.
